阿憨 你来我们酒吧干嘛
Han, what're you doing in our bar?
你明知道酒吧禁止接待未成年人
You know we can't serve kids.
还是你是想看看
Or did you just want to see
一门成功的生意是怎么样
what a successful business looks like?
我知道成功的生意是怎么样啊
I know what a successful business looks like.
我表哥在皇后区开了廉价潜艇堡店
My cousin runs a Blimpie's in Queens.
你有亲戚在廉价潜艇堡店工作啊
You have a relative that works at a Blimpie's?
他单身吗
Is he single?
我叫克林特 我是新来的酒保
Hi, I'm Clint, the new bartender.
你能认识我是你的荣幸
It's a pleasure for you to meet me.
我从街尾那家很酷的酒吧把克林特挖来
I hired Clint away from that cool bar down the street.
他有追随者
He has a following.
而他的追随者追随他到我们这了
And his following followed him here,
所以我们店也有追随者了
and now we have a following.
你能听懂[追随]吗
You following?
追随的粉丝啊
Oh, a following.
在视频网站封掉我裸露视频前 我也有很多啊
Like I had on YouTube before they got all weird about nudity.
老妹 在你这里的人
Girls, this place has more people in it
比我首段婚姻还人多
than my first marriage.
厄尔
Hey, Earl.
给我的梦中情人来一杯可可风暴如何
Cacao Storm for my diabetic dreamboat?
你知道我拒绝不了酒
Well, you know I can't say no to booze.
如果能 我就不会从大牌黑人合唱团被踢走了
If I could, I'd still be in The Temptations.
不不 这里面酒精含量非常少
No, no, no, it's very little booze, okay?
主要卖点是原可可粉
See, you drink it for the raw cacao.
它有助于释放血清素
Yeah, it releases serotonin
激发你的能量 振奋你的心情
and boosts your energy and your mood.
我基本上就是个天才
I'm pretty much a genius.
我基本上还是不喝了吧
And I'm pretty much gonna pass.
想试一杯可可风暴吗 小兄弟
You want to try a Cacao Storm? Huh, buddy?
你当然想喝
Yeah, you do.
它们可让人上瘾了
They're addictive.
原可可粉搭配少量巧克力酒
Raw cacao with a little chocolate liqueur.
我就是靠这个变得远近驰名
It's how I got to be such a big deal.
我也要靠这个卖得特好的饮品
And it's how I'm gonna get a new wardrobe
买新衣服啦
with the way these are selling.
很快我就不用去那种又卖天然气
Soon, I'll be able to buy clothes from places
又卖衣服的店里买衣服了
that don't also sell gas.
我试一杯吧 我最近压力有点大
I'll try one. I am a little stressed.
我要参加今年邮局的
I'm entering the post office's
联邦鸭子邮票大赛
Federal Duck Stamp Contest this year.
这年代了邮局还存在啊
They still have post offices?
真不知道我的那张通缉令还在不在
I wonder if my "Wanted" Poster's still up.
还贴在墙上呢 你小时候超可爱
It is. You were a cute kid.
他们每年都举办比赛
And they have a contest to design
设计新的鸭子邮票图案
a new duck stamp every year.
我要是赢了 我画的绿头鸭
If I win, my mallard drawing will be on
将会印在美国邮票上
official United States postage.
这比赛怎么可能有赢家
How can there be a winner of a contest
参赛的全是人生输家啊
you have to be a loser to enter?
感觉到那股爽劲儿了吗 小弟弟
You feeling the buzz yet, son?
应该会感觉到 我用的可是科伦比亚纯可可
You should. I only use pure Columbian cacao.
全市劲儿最强的 其实是本省最强
Strongest in the city-- actually, in the state.
我不想太显摆而已
I just didn't want to brag about it.
谦虚是我最大的优点之一
It's one of the greatest things about me.
的确 的确有啊
Yes, yes.
我感觉到了 小后劲
I think I feel it. A little jolt.
这是你《美国角斗士》里的艺名吗
Wasn't that your American Gladiator name?
你为啥要来泼老子冷水
Why you got to harsh my buzz?
等我的鸭画荣获桂冠
Wait till this duck flies to stamp victory.
世间再无人敢嘲弄我
Then I'll be ridicule-proof.
但你此生内裤还是会被人拉过头顶
You'll never be wedgie-proof.
我看了一下我们的收入
I just checked our receipts.
我们今晚已经赚了一千五了
We already made $1,500 tonight.
麦克斯 如果能保持
Max, if this keeps up,
我们很快就能买线上视频无广告会员啦
we'll be able to watch Hulu without commercials.
一晚上就有一千五吗
$1,500 in one night?
我当年告发我妈的
I didn't even make that much
悬赏奖金都没那么多
when I turned in my mom for the reward money.
而且这样也比你亲自当酒保靠谱
Plus, it think this is better than you bartending, Max.
你也不错 但你的"你一杯 我也一杯"政策
You were great, but your "One for them, one for me" policy
最后有点无上限[上衣]了
got a little topless.
你难道就没享受那乳头吗
You enjoyed the tips, didn't you?
我是说小费[乳头]
I said "tips."
让让 让让
Excuse me, excuse me.
没在酒吧里见过婴儿推车吗
Haven't you seen a stroller in a bar before?
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
你们连声招呼都不愿意打吗
What, you're not even gonna say hello,
就因为我看起来像一坨垃圾
'cause I look like garbage?
你连让我们打招呼的机会都还没给 苏菲
You didn't even give us a chance, Sophie.
你刚才都在忙着碾过我们的顾客
You were too busy running over all of our customers.
要是我的样子让你觉得丢人了
Well, I'm sorry if I'm embarrassing you
那真是不好意思啊 卡洛琳
with the way I look, Caroline.
我都没时间把我自己
Look, I don't have time to make me
跟芭芭拉宝宝打扮性感
and baby Barbara look sexy.
麦克斯 或许我们可以去做个指甲
Max, maybe we should get manicures?
我上次做指甲还是格温妮丝·帕特罗
I haven't had one since Gwyneth Paltrow
只是稍微讨人厌的那年呢
was only a little annoying.
我们哪来的美容钱啊
We don't have grooming money.
我到现在还像花木兰一样用剑斩头发呢
I'm still cutting my hair with a sword like Mulan.
麦克斯 我们生意这么棒
Max, we're doing really well,
何不稍微享受一下我们的成功呢
so why not enjoy our success a little?
虽然我们还没赚够"去你丫的"钱
I mean, we don't have "screw you" money yet,
但是也够过上只是轻微不爽的日子啦
but we have enough to be mildly unpleasant.
还真是呢
No kiddin'!
快点 快点啊
Oh, come on, come on!
我想快点去做指甲
I want to get our nails did.
为什么总是要这么久才能"完事"
Why does it take so long for a load to finish?
你试过淫声浪语了吗
Have you tried dirty talk?
那是我的烘干机
Oh, that's my dryer.
现在是我的了
Oh, mine now.
走神你就输了
You snooze, you lose.
可我都没走神 怎么会输了呢
But I wasn't snoozing, why am I losing?
最近好吗 珍妮丝
'Sup, Janice?
零钱换钞小铺最近如何
How's things down at the Coinstar?
我准备好要"换"了
I'm ready for a change.
麦克斯 别跟人套近乎 她把我衣服都丢地上了
Max, don't engage her, she threw my clothes on the ground.
比赛开始后 走神你就输了
Buzzer go off? You snooze, you lose.
现在这些都得重新洗过了 因为地上有...
Ugh, now I have to wash these again because there's...
我真心希望地上的是巧克力松糕
what I really hope is fudge on the floor.
我的内裤上哪去了
Where's my underwear?
貌似拉尔夫要去面试 得打扮体面
Looks like Ralph has a job interview.
拉尔夫 那是我的内裤
Ralph, that's my underwear.
还给我
Give it back.
真希望我们能快点不用再来这里
Ugh, I can't wait till we don't have to come here anymore.
那我们以后上哪煮鸡肉啊
But where will we cook our chicken?
你知道吗
You know what?
我们现在是成功人士
We're successful now.
不需要再来这里了
We don't have to come here anymore.
大家能注意我一下吗
Can I have your attention, everyone?
得看了 你是可爱喵星人影片吗
Uh, that depends, are you a cat video?
我想要宣布一件事
I'd like to make an announcement.
从今日起 我们要告别这里
As of today, we are saying good-bye to this place.
拉尔夫 我的内裤你就收下吧
So Ralph, you can keep my panties,
我知道你下个月还有婚礼
I know you have a wedding next month.
我跟麦克斯现在功成名就
Max and I are successful enough now to afford
够钱买自己的洗衣机与烘干机
our own washer and dryer.
实际点说 应该是廉价的请人洗衣服务
Or more realistically, a low-budget fluff-and-fold.
你们可以再看我们一眼
So take one last look at us--
但不需要把你的鸡鸡掏出来 马蒂
But no need to take out your penis, Marty.
走吧 麦克斯 咱们去做指甲去
Come on, Max, let's go get our manicures.
再见啦 自助洗衣店 我们永远不会再回
Good-bye, Laundromat, we are never coming back
你这地狱深渊啦
to this hell hole again.
你刚刚才又洗了一批衣服
You just put another load in the washer.
我们还会再回你这地狱深渊的
We are coming back to this hell hole again.
厄尔 我们做了指甲啦
Earl, we got manicures!
卡洛琳想要我们的指甲透露出成功气息 所以...
Caroline wanted our nails to project success, so...
有什么比大富翁游戏的房子更显示档次呢
What says "Classy lady" like Monopoly houses?
恭喜你啊 麦克斯
Wow, congratulations, Max.
这大概是我们这群人里
This is probably the closest any of us will ever come
最接近拥有房子的一次了
to owning a house.
厄尔 你买不起别牵扯上我们
Speak for yourself, Earl.
麦克斯跟我现在可成功了
Max and I are successful now.
我今早跟自助洗衣店说了再见
I said good-bye to the Laundromat this morning,
今天下午 我跟那家我们去
and this afternoon, I said good-bye to the bodega
打流感疫苗的杂货店说了永别
where we get our flu shots.
你明明可以等到我买完我的
You could've waited till after I got my
流感疫苗加三明治特价套餐再告别
flu shot and sandwich combo.
能麻烦帮我倒杯水吗
Hi, could you bring me a water, please?
如果你手指上有房子
Um, could you bring someone water
你有办法帮人倒水吗
if you had houses for fingers?
真等不及能挥别这地方的时刻
I can't wait till we say good-bye to this place.
我绝对会毒舌到极点
I'm gonna be really mean.
可能写首诗吐槽吧
I may do it as a poem.
有什么跟"鼠辈为患"押韵啊
What rhymes with "Rat-infested"?
"平胸咋办"
Flat-chested.
你别太得意忘形
You better slow down.
我们就只是甜品酒吧生意好了一晚
We've only had one good night at the dessert bar,
你也说我们得在这里继续工作到
and you said we had to keep working at the diner
我们挣够钱升级到"合法"贫穷
till we made enough to be legally poor.
好吧 行
Okay, fine.
感觉那些指甲让你变得通情达理
It's like those nails are making you reasonable
我不喜欢
and I don't like it.
阿憨 你的头发
Han, your hair!
你这是什么造型 爱德华·小憨手吗
Who are you supposed to be, Edward Scissor-hans?
我一晚没睡 都在画我的邮票
I was up all night, sketching my stamp.
想看我的鸭鸭[鸡鸡]吗
Want to see my duck?
祈祷你说的话 不是错别字
Praying that wasn't an auto-correct.
看看这些我练习画的鸭
Look at all the practice ducks I've drawn.
美国木鸭
The American Wood duck.
丑鸭
The Harlequin duck.
斑嘴鸭
The Spot-Billed duck.
绿头鸭
A mallard.
绿头鸭 绿头鸭
A mallard, a mallard--
卡洛琳 把他的电池拔出来
Caroline, take is batteries out.
这只美鸭将会为我赢得大赛
This beauty's gonna win me the stamp contest.
万事俱备 只差上色了
All I have to do now is color it.
然后好好休息 计划我的庆功派对
And then sit back and plan my victory party.
你猜我会用什么邮票来邮寄邀请函
Guess which stamp I'll use to send the invites?
基佬彩虹旗邮票吗
Gay flag?
不 是绿头鸭邮票
No, a mallard!
你从哪弄来的可可粉啊
Where'd you get that cacao from?
克林特收工回家之前留了几克给我
Clint gave me a couple grams before he left last night.
我一整天都微剂量在服用
I've been micro-dosing it all day.
你为什么要直接抹牙龈上啊
Why are you rubbing it on your gums?
长牙嘴痒吗
Are you teething?
克林特说直接吸收爽度更强
Clint says the buzz is stronger if I take it straight.
我本来还不相信克林特说的可可粉会上瘾
Okay, I didn't believe Clint when he said cacao was addictive,
但我本来也不相信爱尔兰矮妖是真的
but I also didn't believe in leprechauns
但在矮妖店里做事后我就信了
until I started working for one.
如果我把牙龈割开
If I cut my gums...
粉会不会更快进入我的血管啊
Will it enter my bloodstream any faster?
老毒虫你应该懂啊
You're a junkie!
阿憨 你又跟上次喝完整瓶红牛一样嗨了
Han, you're acting like that time you had a whole Red Bull.
好了
Okay...
你上瘾了
you have a problem!
我会告诉克林特不许再供应你
I'm telling Clint you're cut off.
那我要告诉克林特我爱他
Well, I'm telling Clint I love him.
他就爱听这个
He loves that.
行 我只好不靠可可粉完成我的邮票了
Fine, I'll just finish my stamp without cacao.
去你的
Damn it!
大家安安
Hi, everybody!
我希望他们永远都不指望
I hope they're never expecting Barbara
芭芭拉开始有任何短期记忆
to have a short-term memory.
别看了 别看我了
Oh, look away, look away.
情况越来越糟糕了
Things have gotten real bad.
我现在看起来像你们这帮人了
I look like all of you now.
苏菲 你为什么不跟我们一起去做指甲
Sophie, why didn't you come with us to the nail place?
可好玩了
It was so much fun.
我去不了 太忙了
I couldn't make it, I was too busy
忙着给芭芭拉的尿布贴亮片
bedazzling Barbara's diapers.
我只能接受这个事实了
I'm just gonna have to face it--
我至少有12年的时间不能再美艳动人了
I'm not gonna be pretty again for at least 12 years.
天啊 到时候我就到了卡洛琳的岁数了
Oh, I'll be Caroline's age by then.
苏菲 我总是告诉你 你在我眼里永远性感
Sophie, I keep saying, you'll always be sexy to me.
我不想说些情意绵绵的肉麻情话
And I hate to sound all lovey-dovey,
但我的鸡因你而勃
but you're giving me a boner.
你是因为没得选才这么说
You're just saying that 'cause you have to.
我才不要你的可怜勃
I don't want your pity boner.
卡洛琳 如果真有可怜勃这回事
Caroline, if pity boners are a thing,
那你得赶紧重出江湖啊
you have got to get back out there.
我刚才也在想同一件事
I was thinking the same thing.
克林特 你带货来了吗
You got the stuff, Clint?
是顶级货吧
It's premium grade, right?
如果不是 那你就准备接受
If it isn't, you're in for a very
一场不太愉快的交谈了
unpleasant conversation.
我哥伦比亚的供货商跟我保证过
My guy from Columbia guarantees it.
不是那个毒品大国 是我哥伦比亚大学的同学
Not the country, we went to college together.
想验个货吗
Want a little taste?
废话 还用你说
You bet your butt I do!
我想确定里面没有掺杂便宜雀巢咖啡粉
I want to make sure it's not cut with Nestle Quik.
脏驴鸡尾酒就是用这种货调的
That's the stuff muddy donkeys are made of.
麦克斯
Max!
没想到在这遇见你
Uh, fancy meeting you here.
我和克林特在叙兄弟情呢 聊聊...
Clint and I were just bro-ing out over...
运动啊
sports.
大胸啊
And breasts.
还有...动物园啊
And...zoos?
男人平时见面都聊什么呀
What do men talk about?
麦克斯
Hey, Max.
昨晚我们赚翻了 对吧
We killed it last night, huh?
我的功劳大过你哦
Me more than you.
你到底要不要 我得去做我的播客了
You gonna want this or not, I got to go do my podcast.
我要采访我自己
I'm interviewing myself.
是不是毒品交易 我一看就能看出来
I know a drug deal when I see it!
他不许碰毒
He's cut off.
就像2元酒之夜 我不许碰酒一样
Like me on $2 margarita night.
麦克斯 我需要可可粉来完成我的鸭子邮票
Max, I need that cacao to finish my duck stamp!
让这匹巧克力小马再带我飞最后一次吧
One last ride on the chocolate pony.
瞧瞧你 满脸都是巧克力
Look at you-- chocolate all over your face.
你就像《军火贩》的肥男主在看影评 爽得咧
You look like Jonah Hill reading the reviews for War Dogs.
克林特 你不许卖给他
Clint, don't you dare sell it to him.
轮不到你告诉我该怎么做
You can't tell me what to do, okay?
我是说真的 我会辞职的哦
I'm serious--I will quit.
那把我对我妈说的同一句话送给你
Oh, hmm, I'll say the same thing I said to my mother--
接受请辞
resignation accepted.
你犯了一个天大的错误
You just made a huge mistake.
不用你说我也知道
You're talking to someone
我可是看了《真探》第二季的人
who watched the second season of True Detective.
你说是吧 阿憨
Right, Han?
那个人渣不可能把全部可可粉都带走吧
That scumbag couldn't have taken all the cacao.
快 帮我找找酒柜有没有
Quick, help me check the cabinets.
别碰我的抽屉[内裤] 阿憨
Keep away from my drawers, Han.
这句话你肯定整天听到
You got to be used to hearing that.
麦克斯 我刚跟免费诊所告别了
Max, I just gave a good-bye speech at the free clinic.
对了 那个实验室技术员
Oh, also, the lab technician
让你尽快打给她
said for you to call her ASAP.
克莱尔什么事都爱大惊小怪
Ugh, Claire freaks out about everything.
我要把这地方翻个底朝天
I'll tear this place apart!
可可粉到底在哪里
Where the hell is the cacao?
发生什么事了 克林特去哪儿了
What's happening, where's Clint?
-他辞职了 -他辞职了
- He quit. - He quit?
但他的追随者怎么办
But what about his following?
我们的追随者怎么办
What about our following?
我的告别巡回秀怎么办
What about my good-bye tour?
跟你的告别秀告别啊
Say good-bye to it.
我好像找到了点
I think I found some!
不是 那是纯灰尘
Nope, that was straight-up dirt.
这样最好
It's for the best.
因为那位可可粉小姐已经走火入魔了
'Cause Jane Cacaoski over there can't get enough.
我回吧台后面[监狱]工作了
I'll just get back behind the bar.
抱歉先失陪啦 其中一间牢房的犯人跑出来了
Now, if you'll excuse me, one of my hotels came loose
都怪我当时忙着对人竖中指没看好
while I was giving someone the finger.
我想我只能打给广告分类网上
I guess I'm going to have to call that other dealer
另一位粉贩子了
I found on Craigslist.
我是老鼠 我要我的大米
I'm Ice-T and I need my Coco.
阿憨 如果你能拿到可可粉
Han, if you can get that cacao,
麦克斯自己也能做可可风暴
Max can make the Cacao Storms herself.
我见过她用罂粟籽面包圈和气泡水做出鸦片
I've seen her make opium out of poppy seed bagels and a Lacroix.
阿憨 快打给粉贩子
Han, call that dealer.
已经拨出去了
Already dialing.
我已经在去"后庭"的半路上了
I'm halfway down the Hershey Highway.
我是说软糖工厂
I meant the Fudge Factory.
我不想知道你的私生活
I don't want to hear about your personal life,
快打电话吧
just call the dealer.
阿憨 那家伙在哪儿
Han, where is this guy?
我好害怕啊
I'm scared.
别人可能会误会我们是情侣
Someone might think we're a couple.
我也想他马上来啊
I hope he gets here soon.
我刚吸食了一品脱的冰淇淋
I just snorted a pint of Chunky Monkey.
他来了 淡定点
That's him, now act cool.
毒贩子先生 你好呀
Yoo-hoo, Mr. Drug Dealer!
这边
Right here.
你真让我丢脸
You're embarrassing me!
对了 记得告诉他我们不是情侣
Oh, also, tell him we're not a couple.
你们俩是来买可可粉的吗
You guys here for the cacao?
废话少说 货在哪儿
Let's cut to the chase, where's the dope?
我面前就有一蠢货
Standing right in front of me.
我们不是情侣哦
We're not together.
你们想让警察听见吗
You want the cops to hear us?
有关系吗 你是在卖巧克力粉
Would it matter? You're selling chocolate.
我知道 但假装违法感觉更好玩啊
I know, but it's more fun to act like it's naughty.
这是我干这行的唯一原因
That's the only reason I do this.
我无聊死了
I'm so bored.
我是一名全职爷爷
I'm a stay-at-home grandpa.
给我看街粉
Show me the skrank!
这是我为街头可可粉专门编造的一个词
That's the word I made up for street cacao.
在这
Here it is.
为了得到它 我还杀了一名妓女
Had to kill a hooker to get it.
瞎说的啦
I wish.
我的儿媳妇在雀巢工作
My daughter-in-law works for Nestle.
厄尔 你在这里干嘛
Earl, what're you doing out here?
先把话说清楚 我跟阿憨在这里
Just to be clear, I'm out here with Han
纯粹是公事 绝对没私情
for business, nothing romantic.
你们在外面私会
What are you doing out here
我的加拿大伟哥供货商干嘛
with my Canadian Viagra connection?
-厄尔 -比尔
- Hey, Earl! - Hey, Bill!
伙计 你的儿媳妇还好吗
Hey, man, how's your daughter-in-law?
还在多伦多的雀巢公司想着往上爬吗
Still climbing the corporate ladder at Nestle Toronto?
然后周末健健身
And doing CrossFit on the weekends.
泰德终于拿到真正的房产证了
And Ted's finally got his real estate license.
没人想听 老爷爷
No one cares, Grandpa!
你去跟公园里的鸽子唠家常吧
Tell that to the pigeons in the park!
老子都快要把巧克力糖注射进静脉了
I'm this close to main-lining Tootsie Rolls.
-给你钱 -不是吧
- Here's the money. - Not this again!
我就出来想抽支大麻烟
I come out here to smoke a joint,
就这么让我撞见毒品交易吗
and I walk in on a drug deal?
可耻
Shame!
你
Hey, you!
快离开这 否则我就让你的面包车吃枪子儿
Get out of here before I pop a cap in your Honda Odyssey.
抱歉 要么干这行 要么干小三
I'm sorry, it was either this, or have an affair.
而我实在没那个体力啊
And I'm just too tired.
看来我要告诉露丝
Well, it looks like I got to go tell Ruth
今晚将会是"除了爱爱啥都行"之夜
it's gonna be an "everything but" kind of night
哎
Jeez.
这都是跟你学的 父亲大人
I learned it from watching you, Dad?
麦克斯 我们的甜品酒吧需要可可粉
Max, we need that cacao for our dessert bar.
我已经跟救济厨房说了我对他们
I already told the soup kitchen what I think
番茄浓汤的真实想法 所以我们没有回头路了
of their tomato bisque, so there's no turning back.
你们俩的瘾头都失控了
Your addictions are both out of control.
卡洛琳 成功没有捷径
Caroline, there are no shortcuts to success
创造一只能登上邮票的鸭子也是
or creating a stamp-worthy mallard.
人生需要缓慢稳步往上爬
Life is a slow, steady climb
才能好好过活
to just getting by.
快振作起来
Snap out of it!
别光说我 你也上瘾啊
Me? You're addicted too.
对象是你的美甲
To these nails.
我才没有 我随时能打住
No I'm not, I can stop any time!
那你哭屁啊
Then why are you crying?
因为老娘在一条巷子里双膝跪地
'Cause I'm on my knees in an alley
却没有任何让我爽的事情发生
and nothing fun is happening!
破坏我"家"庭
Home wrecker!
好啊
You know, fine!
或许我是迷上它们给我的感觉
Maybe I like the way they make me feel.
可你呢 你如此热衷于成功
But you--you were so high on success,
你甚至愿意让阿憨吸粉过度
you were willing to let Han OD!
或者至少变得非常非常活跃过度
Or, at least, get really, really hyper-active.
那又怎样 你又不在乎我 麦克斯 对吗
So what? You don't care about me, Max, do you?
对啊
No.
或许有一点吧
Maybe a little.
瞧你的瘾头对我造成多大的影响了吧 卡洛琳
See how your addiction has affected me, Caroline?
害我刚不得不承认我在乎阿憨
I just had to admit I care about Han!
现在我真是开心到飞起啊
Now I'm flying high on that!
我要去试着完成我的邮票
I'm gonna go try to finish my stamp.
或许来杯热可可会有帮助
Perhaps some hot cocoa would help.
当然是指直接从直肠灌
Administered rectally, of course.
找到了
Found it!
苏菲
Sophie?
怎么今晚所有熟人都在这条巷子里
Is there anyone we know not in this alley?
我找到芭芭拉的水钻定型机了
I found Barbara's bedazzler.
是啊 现在啥事都以她为主
Oh, yeah, it's all about her now.
很难同时做到外表美美哒 母爱棒棒哒
Oh, you can't be gorgeous and be a good mother.
你看尼尔·帕特里克·哈里斯就知道了
Just look at Neil Patrick Harris.
我觉得他非常有个人魅力
Well, I think he's very charming
你这么说不公平了
and I think you're being unfair.
这话可能是来自我剩余的美甲 但苏菲
This might be what's left of my nails talking, but Sophie,
如果你不再用酥胸半露装饰自己
if you're not decked out with your boobs half showing,
你是不是会给芭芭拉树立错误的榜样呢
are you really setting the right example for Barbara?
对于身处垃圾箱中的我
Oh, from this side of the dumpster,
你这话的确让我获益良多 姑娘
you're making a lot of sense, girl.
还真是
You really are.
你要开始刷牙
Are you gonna start brushing your teeth
把马桶盖放下来了吗
and putting the seat down?
并没有
No.
这是你的果馅饼提尼
Here's your flan-tini.
这杯是我的果馅饼提尼
And here's my flan-tini.
重回岗位感觉真好
Good to be back.
我试过了 但就是找不到克林特
Well, I tried, but I can't find Clint.
感觉就像我 跟男人上完床就跑没影一样
I feel like every man I've ever had sex with.
我们才不需要克林特或他的傻逼可可粉
We don't need Clint or his stupid cacao.
但是 他的播客还挺有意思的呢
Uh, although, his podcast was pretty interesting.
他的两位女老板听起来简直就是女魔头啊
Those girls he worked for sounded like nightmares.
我要来一 二 三杯雪碧
I'm gonna have one, two, three Sprites.
我们今晚想玩得野一点
We're getting wild tonight.
马上来 药头比尔
Coming right up, Bill the Dealer.
现在就只是比尔了
Oh, it's just Bill now.
手机意外在我进行重大抗胃酸药交易时
I accidentally butt-dialed my wife during a major
打给了我老婆
Pepcid AC drop.
她把面包车没收了
She took the minivan.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
不 我不是不老女星苏珊娜·萨默斯
No, it's not Suzanne Somers.
是我 苏菲
It's me, Sophie!
苏菲又回性感艳后路线了
Wow, Sophie got her sexy back.
还有艳胸跟艳穴
Yeah, and front and under.
苏菲 这杯果馅饼提尼是你应得的
Sophie, you deserve a flan-tini.
也是我应得的
And so do I.
我按你让我做的方法做
Oh, you know what, I did what you told me to do
然后把芭芭拉宝宝送到了训练师兼保姆那里
and I dropped baby Barbara off at the trainer/babysitter,
然后再让一帮韩国女人帮我修剪"杂毛"
and I had a bunch of Korean ladies go to town on me.
奥列格呢
Hey, where's Oleg?
我告诉他在这里跟我碰面
I told him to meet me here.
苏菲
Sophie?
你今日美艳动人的程度
You look as beautiful as the day
犹如我们首次在洗手槽做爱的那天
we first did it on the sink.
他妈还用你说
Damn straight, I do!
你为什么穿着白人佬的衣服
Yo, what's with the white people's clothes?
对啊 这是怎么回事 连乳头都没露
Yeah, what's going on? I can't even see any nipple.
但却反而比以前更糟
But somehow, it's worse.
苏菲 我想让你看到
Sophie, I want you to see that
我们不用像以前那样永远都当性感夫妻
we don't have to be the sexy couple anymore.
什么不用像以前
Anymore?
你们俩什么时候当过性感夫妻了
When were you guys the sexy couple?
你们去阿米什人区的那个周末吗
That weekend you went to Amish Country?
赞啊
Oh, yeah.
还记得我们在那家人面前
Do you remember when we did it in that buggy
在马车上做爱的画面吗
in front of that family?
我敢赌他们当时一定很想拍下来
Oh, I bet they wish they had a camera for that.
想跟我去厕所做爱吗
You want to go do it in the bathroom...
用马车式
buggy-style?
我会假装那阿米什哥们
Oh, I'm gonna pretend that Jebediah
因为羞愧而别过头 没在看
is turning away in shame.
我会假装他没有 继续盯着看
I'm gonna pretend he isn't.
看来晚点我们得给厕所大清洗了
I guess we're scrubbing down our bathroom later.
我们要走啦
We're heading out.
马上要八点了
It's almost 8:00.
这是我最后一包可可粉
Here's my last bag of cacao.
我处理不掉它
I can't do anything with it,
我胆固醇过高
not with my cholesterol.
一小包可可粉
A tiny baggie of cacao?
我们能拿这干嘛
What're we gonna do with this?
跟所有我发现的粉末一样
Same thing I do with any powder I find:
试试它牛逼在哪
see what all the fuss is about.
还不赖
Not hating it.
藏私货吗
Holding out on me?
你俩街粉小婊子
You skrank skanks!
我也要来分一口粉
I'm coming in!